copper?
どう?
Natsumi-chan.
なつみちゃん
Are you starting to want it?
欲しくなってきた?
It's about time...
そろそろ...
want?
欲しい?
You're forgetting something important.
大事なことを忘れてるよ
I'm forgetting something important.
大事なことを忘れてる
This is an interview...
これ面接だから...
It's an interview, so there's no pay.
面接だからギャラがないよ
What should I do?
どうする?
Not at all.
全然ない
Is that okay?
それでもいい?
Do you still want it?
それでも欲しいの?
TRUE?
本当?
Are you going to sleep?
寝るの?
good?
いい?
Which one should you get the most?
一番手に入れておくの?
Even though it's an interview.
面接なのにね
What happened to the interview?
面接どうした?
Have you seen it?
見たことある?
Something like this.
こんなの
do not have.
ない
I'll do it.
やっちゃう
why?
なんで?
people?
人?
Even though it's an interview.
面接なのにね
Uncle's neighborhood.
おじさんのお近所
It's so cool.
えっきらね
Even though I'm 19 years old.
19歳なのにね
The vibration.
振動が
The vibration is in my house.
振動がうちにちんじゃん
Virture is coming after all.
やっぱりバーチャー来るのじゃん
It's an interview.
面接だよ
interview.
面接
I cum during the interview.
面接で中出したよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
I can't help it?
しょうがない?
I can't help it.
しょうがない
It can't be helped.
しょうがないね
Because it feels good.
気持ちいいから
So let's take a proper photo this time.
じゃあ今度はちゃんと撮ろうね
There's a guarantee this time.
今度はギャラあるからね
It can't be helped.
しょうがないですね
Hey, can I do that?
これちょっとさあ、 あれしていい?
I guess I'll have to take a look.
ちょっとね、観察しないとね
Because I have to observe it.
観 察しないといけないから
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くね?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Please lend it to me.
貸してね
Tell me if it hurts.
痛かったら言ってね
There you are.
いますね
I'm here.
いますよ
There was a lot of silence from a lot of old men.
大量の、 大量のおじさんの静粛が
yes.
はい
thank you.
ありがとう
I was able to take a picture.
撮れた
When I pull this out, it comes out sluggish.
これをね、 抜くときがね、 ダラって出てくるんで
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
ほらほらほらほらほらほら
I was able to take so many pictures.
こんなに撮れました
Look, you can take so many pictures.
こんなに撮れてるほら
Are you there?
いる?
There was a lot of silence during the interview today.
今日はね、面接でこんだけ静粛が出ましたということで
See you then.
じゃあまた
Let's take another photo.
また 撮りましょう
See you then.
じゃあ ね
bye bye.
バイバイ